[
  {
    "questionNum": 78001,
    "questionText": " Escape Velocity from the earth is ?:",
    "answerText": " 11 Km per Sec."
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78002,
    "questionText": " How many rings on the Olympic flag",
    "answerText": " Five"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78003,
    "questionText": " What colour is Spock's blood",
    "answerText": " Green"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78004,
    "questionText": " Where in your body is your patella",
    "answerText": " Knee ( it's the kneecap )"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78005,
    "questionText": " Where can you find London bridge today",
    "answerText": " USA ( Arizona )"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78006,
    "questionText": " Who was the first man in space",
    "answerText": " Yuri Gagarin"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78007,
    "questionText": " Which animal lays eggs",
    "answerText": " Duck billed platypus"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78008,
    "questionText": " Who's band was The Quarrymen",
    "answerText": " John Lenon"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78009,
    "questionText": " What does a funambulist do",
    "answerText": " Tightrope walker"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78010,
    "questionText": " Who invented the television",
    "answerText": " John Logie Baird"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78011,
    "questionText": " How many feet in a fathom",
    "answerText": " Six"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78012,
    "questionText": " Who sailed in the Nina - Pinta and Santa Maria",
    "answerText": " Christopher Columbus"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78013,
    "questionText": " Which leader died in St Helena",
    "answerText": " Napoleon Bonaparte"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78014,
    "questionText": " Who wrote Gone with the Wind",
    "answerText": " Margaret Mitchell"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78015,
    "questionText": " Whose nose grew when he told a lie",
    "answerText": " Pinocchio"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78016,
    "questionText": " Who has won the most Oscars",
    "answerText": " Walt Disney"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78017,
    "questionText": " If you had pogonophobia what would you be afraid of",
    "answerText": " Beards"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78018,
    "questionText": " What was the first James Bond book",
    "answerText": " Casino Royal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78019,
    "questionText": " What is the currency of Austria",
    "answerText": " Schilling"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78020,
    "questionText": " Air Lingus is the national airline of which country",
    "answerText": " Republic of Ireland or Eire"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78021,
    "questionText": " What is a baby rabbit called",
    "answerText": " Kit or Kitten"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78022,
    "questionText": " Ictheologists study what",
    "answerText": " Fish"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78023,
    "questionText": " Who or what lives in a formicarium",
    "answerText": " Ants"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78024,
    "questionText": " What type of acid is used in car batteries",
    "answerText": " Sulphuric"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78025,
    "questionText": " Christopher Cockerel invented what",
    "answerText": " Hovercraft"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78026,
    "questionText": " La Giaconda is better known as what",
    "answerText": " Mona Lisa"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78027,
    "questionText": " Eric Arthur Blaire was the real name of which author",
    "answerText": " George Orwell"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78028,
    "questionText": " What was the first James Bond film",
    "answerText": " Dr No"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78029,
    "questionText": " What was the capital of Ethiopia",
    "answerText": " Addis Ababa"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78030,
    "questionText": " What is the largest state in the USA",
    "answerText": " Alaska"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78031,
    "questionText": " Which human rights organisation founded 1961 got Nobel 1977",
    "answerText": " Amnesty International"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78032,
    "questionText": " Whose autobiography was The long walk to Freedom",
    "answerText": " Nelson Mandela"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78033,
    "questionText": " What was discovered in 1922 by Howard Carter",
    "answerText": " Tutankamen tomb"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78034,
    "questionText": " Clyde Tonbaugh discovered what planet in 1930",
    "answerText": " Pluto"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78035,
    "questionText": " Who ran through the streets naked crying Eureka Archimedes"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78036,
    "questionText": " In which city was Alexander Graham Bell born in 1847",
    "answerText": " Edinburgh"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78037,
    "questionText": " What is the national flower of Japan",
    "answerText": " Chrysanthemum"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78038,
    "questionText": " What did mathematician John Napier invent in 1614",
    "answerText": " Logarithms"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78039,
    "questionText": " Consumption was the former name of which disease",
    "answerText": " Tuberculosis"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78040,
    "questionText": " Who wrote Gulliver’s Travels",
    "answerText": " Jonathon Swift"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78041,
    "questionText": " In Japan what is Seppuku",
    "answerText": " Hari Kari - suicide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78042,
    "questionText": " Who discovered blood circulation",
    "answerText": " William Harvey"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78043,
    "questionText": " Why is Louise Brown - born 1978 famous",
    "answerText": " First test tube baby"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78044,
    "questionText": " The title of whose book translates as my struggle",
    "answerText": " Adolf Hitler"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78045,
    "questionText": " Carlo Collodi created which famous children's character",
    "answerText": " Pinocchio"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78046,
    "questionText": " 1656 Christian Huygens invented what type of timekeeper",
    "answerText": " Pendulum clock"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78047,
    "questionText": " What animals name translates as water horse",
    "answerText": " Hippopotamus"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78048,
    "questionText": " In 1643 Evangalisa Torichelli invented the first what",
    "answerText": " Barometer"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78049,
    "questionText": " What is the longest river in Italy",
    "answerText": " Po"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78050,
    "questionText": " What does a polyandric women have more than one of",
    "answerText": " Husband"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78051,
    "questionText": " In 1911 the archaeologist Hiram Bingham discovered what lost city",
    "answerText": " Machu Picchu"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78052,
    "questionText": " In 1901 which brand of car was seen for the first time",
    "answerText": " Mercedes"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78053,
    "questionText": " Brisbane is the state capital of which SE Australian state",
    "answerText": " Queensland"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78054,
    "questionText": " What is the capitol of Morocco",
    "answerText": " Rabat"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78055,
    "questionText": " Linus Torwalds invented and wrote what",
    "answerText": " Linux computer operating system"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78056,
    "questionText": " Zambia and Zimbabwe used to be called what",
    "answerText": " Rhodesia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78057,
    "questionText": " What is the staple food of one third of the worlds population",
    "answerText": " Rice"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78058,
    "questionText": " What digit does not exist in Roman Numerals",
    "answerText": " Zero"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78059,
    "questionText": " Who was nicknames The desert Fox",
    "answerText": " Erwin Rommel"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78060,
    "questionText": " Who performed the first heart transplant in South Africa",
    "answerText": " Christian Barnard"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78061,
    "questionText": " What is the common name for the star Sirius",
    "answerText": " Dog Star"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78062,
    "questionText": " What calculating aid was invented by William Oughtred in 1662",
    "answerText": " Slide Rule"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78063,
    "questionText": " Which Athenian philosopher wrote nothing –but immortalised by Plato",
    "answerText": " Socrates"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78064,
    "questionText": " Which European country is divided into areas called Cantons",
    "answerText": " Switzerland"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78065,
    "questionText": " Which medical tool was developed by Sanctorius in 1612",
    "answerText": " Thermometer"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78066,
    "questionText": " Who created Tarzan (all names) in 1914",
    "answerText": " Edgar Rice Burroughs"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78067,
    "questionText": " Camellia Sinesis evergreen shrub better known as what",
    "answerText": " Tea"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78068,
    "questionText": " In 1901 who first transmitted radio signals across Atlantic",
    "answerText": " Marconi"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78069,
    "questionText": " Viticulture is the growing of what plants",
    "answerText": " Vines"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78070,
    "questionText": " Angel falls Venezuela Highest whaterfalls but where second Highest",
    "answerText": " Yosemite USA"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78071,
    "questionText": " What was the first credit card",
    "answerText": " Diners Club"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78072,
    "questionText": " What was Charles Dickens last (unfinished) novel",
    "answerText": " Mystery of Edwin Drood"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78073,
    "questionText": " Which sea on Earth has no beaches",
    "answerText": " Sargasso sea"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78074,
    "questionText": " De Witt Wallace founded what",
    "answerText": " Readers Digest"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78075,
    "questionText": " Who did the USA buy the Virgin islands from",
    "answerText": " Denmark"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78076,
    "questionText": " Which country was the first to introduce old age pensions",
    "answerText": " Germany"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78077,
    "questionText": " Who was the Roman god of agriculture",
    "answerText": " Saturn"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78078,
    "questionText": " What is ikebana",
    "answerText": " Flower arranging"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78079,
    "questionText": " Goa used to be a colony of which nation",
    "answerText": " Portugal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78080,
    "questionText": " Hypermetropic people are what",
    "answerText": " Long Sighted"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78081,
    "questionText": " Which leader lives in the Potola",
    "answerText": " Dalai Lama"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78082,
    "questionText": " What wood was the cross supposed to be made of",
    "answerText": " Mistletoe"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78083,
    "questionText": " Scotopic people can do what",
    "answerText": " See in the dark"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78084,
    "questionText": " In Japan what colour car is reserved for the royal family only",
    "answerText": " Maroon"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78085,
    "questionText": " What is a baby whale called",
    "answerText": " Calf"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78086,
    "questionText": " Who wrote Les Miserable",
    "answerText": " Victor Hugo"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78087,
    "questionText": " Who rode a horse called Bucephalus",
    "answerText": " Alexander the Great"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78088,
    "questionText": " What is the largest environmental organisation in the world ?",
    "answerText": " Greenpeace"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78089,
    "questionText": " In Greek mythology Deianeira was the wife of who ?",
    "answerText": " Hercules"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78090,
    "questionText": " Who is the Patron Saint of boy scouts ?",
    "answerText": " Saint George"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78091,
    "questionText": " In his will who left his wife his second best bed ?",
    "answerText": " William Shakespeare"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78092,
    "questionText": " first found"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78093,
    "questionText": " Old Dominion was a nickname of which US state ?",
    "answerText": " Virginia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78094,
    "questionText": " In Islam what is the third piller of wisdom ?",
    "answerText": " Charity - 2.5 % of income (there's 5 in total)"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78095,
    "questionText": " The religious text Mishna comes from which religion ?",
    "answerText": " Judaism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78096,
    "questionText": " The Zagros mountain range is in which country ?",
    "answerText": " Iran"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78097,
    "questionText": " Who released the album Invincible ?",
    "answerText": " Michael Jackson"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78098,
    "questionText": " 28 Which order of monks are famous for their silence ?",
    "answerText": " Trappist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78099,
    "questionText": " Which pop singer was nicknamed ?",
    "answerText": " The Groover from Vancouver Brian Adams"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78100,
    "questionText": " Name the first war submarine invented by David Bushnell ?",
    "answerText": " Turtle"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78101,
    "questionText": " Peter Parker is the alter ego of which superhero ?",
    "answerText": " Spiderman"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78102,
    "questionText": " In which city was Galileo born ?",
    "answerText": " Pisa"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78103,
    "questionText": " Which detective dies in The Final Problem ?",
    "answerText": " Sherlock Holmes"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78104,
    "questionText": " Narita is the main airport of which city ?",
    "answerText": " Tokyo"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78105,
    "questionText": " What is the more common name of Sildenafil Citrate ?",
    "answerText": " Viagra"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78106,
    "questionText": " Who owned a sword called crocea mors or yellow death ?",
    "answerText": " Julius Caesar"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78107,
    "questionText": " The Sejm are the legislative body in which country ?",
    "answerText": " Poland"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78108,
    "questionText": " Wilma Rudolf first black US woman to win Olympic gold where ?",
    "answerText": " Rome in 1960"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78109,
    "questionText": " Sergey Bubka broke world record over 30 times in which event ?",
    "answerText": " Pole Vault"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78110,
    "questionText": " Which car company was founded by Sir William Lyons in 1922 ?",
    "answerText": " Jaguar"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78111,
    "questionText": " Calamine is the ore what is the product ?",
    "answerText": " Zinc"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78112,
    "questionText": " In Finland who rides a goat named Ukko ?",
    "answerText": " Santa Clause"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78113,
    "questionText": " Fado is a musical style popular in which country ?",
    "answerText": " Portugal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78114,
    "questionText": " What is the sacred animal of Thailand ?",
    "answerText": " The white elephant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78115,
    "questionText": " Lahnaphophobia is the fear of what ?",
    "answerText": " Vegetables"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78116,
    "questionText": " The Westminster is the oldest and biggest what in the USA ?",
    "answerText": " Dog Show"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78117,
    "questionText": " Which animals make a sound called nuzzing ?",
    "answerText": " Camels"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78118,
    "questionText": " Anhedonia is the inability to feel what ?",
    "answerText": " Pleasure"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78119,
    "questionText": " What does a hygrometer measure ?",
    "answerText": " Humidity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78120,
    "questionText": " Azote is the old name for what element ?",
    "answerText": " Nitrogen"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78121,
    "questionText": " What is sometimes referred to as Zulu time ?",
    "answerText": " Greenwich mean time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78122,
    "questionText": " Tasseomancy is fortune telling using what ?",
    "answerText": " Tea Leaves"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78123,
    "questionText": " A Cruciverbalist is interested in what ?",
    "answerText": " Crossword Puzzles"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78124,
    "questionText": " വില്ലേജ് എക്സ്റ്റൻഷൻ ഓഫിസർ, എൽ .ഡി .സി  പരീക്ഷകൾക്ക് വേണ്ടിയുള്ള മലയാളം ചോദ്യോത്തരങ്ങൾ {കേരളം, ഇന്ത്യ, സയൻസ്} എന്നിവ പ്രസിദ്ധികരിച്ചിട്ടുണ്ട്. എല്ലാവരും പ്രയോജനപ്പെടുത്തുമല്ലോ. 30000+ English General Knowledge വിവിധ വിഷയങ്ങളില്‍ ഉള്‍പ്പെടുത്തിയിട്ടുണ്ട്. University Assistant, KAS, തുടങ്ങിയ പരീക്ഷകളള്‍ക്കായി പ്രത്യേകം ചോദ്യങ്ങള്‍ ഉണ്ട്. Ebook Store ല്‍ MOBILE FRIENDLY EBOOKS പ്രസിദ്ധികരിക്കുന്നതാണ്.  ",
    "answerText": " എല്ലാവരുടെയും സഹകരണം തുടര്‍ന്നും പ്രതീക്ഷിക്കുന്നു. സഹകരിക്കുമല്ലോ, ADMIN, Gk4succss "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78125,
    "questionText": " കേരളത്തിന്‍റെ നെല്ലറ എന്നറിയപ്പെടുന്ന ജില്ല ",
    "answerText": " പാലക്കാട് "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78126,
    "questionText": " Being unable to pay one's debt",
    "answerText": " Insolvent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78127,
    "questionText": " The study of the functions of the body",
    "answerText": " Physiology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78128,
    "questionText": " The science of for telling events by stars",
    "answerText": " Astrology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78129,
    "questionText": " Government by officials in a state",
    "answerText": " Bureaucracy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78130,
    "questionText": " An office without any work but high pay",
    "answerText": " Sinecure"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78131,
    "questionText": " A medicine to counteract the effect of a poison.",
    "answerText": " Antidote"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78132,
    "questionText": " Word for word",
    "answerText": " Verbatim"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78133,
    "questionText": " Wish to do good to others",
    "answerText": " Benevolence"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78134,
    "questionText": " Whose meaning is difficult to understand",
    "answerText": " Abstruse"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78135,
    "questionText": " Way out for water or steam",
    "answerText": " Outlet"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78136,
    "questionText": " Want of sleep",
    "answerText": " Insomnia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78137,
    "questionText": " Usual behaviour of a social group",
    "answerText": " Custom"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78138,
    "questionText": " Use of mild words in place of words required by truth.",
    "answerText": " Euphemism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78139,
    "questionText": " Troops trained for being dropped by parachute",
    "answerText": " Paratroops"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78140,
    "questionText": " Touch or stroke lovingly",
    "answerText": " Fondle / Caress"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78141,
    "questionText": " A traditional story related to deities",
    "answerText": " Myth"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78142,
    "questionText": " That which is pig like",
    "answerText": " Porcine"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78143,
    "questionText": " Thing to be corrected in a printed book",
    "answerText": " Corrigendum"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78144,
    "questionText": " Things taken by robbers",
    "answerText": " Booty"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78145,
    "questionText": " That which is lion like",
    "answerText": " Leonine"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78146,
    "questionText": " That which is fox like",
    "answerText": " Vulpine"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78147,
    "questionText": " That which is dog like",
    "answerText": " Canine"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78148,
    "questionText": " That which exists separately from other people",
    "answerText": " Independent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78149,
    "questionText": " That which can not be perceived by touch",
    "answerText": " Intangible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78150,
    "questionText": " That which can not be calculated",
    "answerText": " Incalculable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78151,
    "questionText": " That which can be rooted out",
    "answerText": " Eradicable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78152,
    "questionText": " Study of the development of plants and animals from earlier forms",
    "answerText": " Genealogy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78153,
    "questionText": " Study of oceans and their phenomena",
    "answerText": " Oceanography"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78154,
    "questionText": " Study of law",
    "answerText": " Nomology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78155,
    "questionText": " Study of fossils",
    "answerText": " Paleontology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78156,
    "questionText": " Study of ancient things like tombs, buried towns",
    "answerText": " Archaeology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78157,
    "questionText": " Strong desire for food, wealth",
    "answerText": " Greed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78158,
    "questionText": " Strong dislike between two persons",
    "answerText": " Antipathy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78159,
    "questionText": " Stream flowing into another big river",
    "answerText": " Tributary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78160,
    "questionText": " Stealing from the writings of others",
    "answerText": " Plagiarism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78161,
    "questionText": " Statement that is obviously true",
    "answerText": " Platitude"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78162,
    "questionText": " That which can be easily believed",
    "answerText": " Credible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78163,
    "questionText": " That which can not be put out or extinguished",
    "answerText": " Inextinguishable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78164,
    "questionText": " That which can not be satisfied",
    "answerText": " Insatiable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78165,
    "questionText": " That which can not be erased or removed",
    "answerText": " Indelible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78166,
    "questionText": " That which can easily be curved without breaking",
    "answerText": " Flexible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78167,
    "questionText": " That which can not be corrupted",
    "answerText": " Incorruptible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78168,
    "questionText": " To escape from hard realities",
    "answerText": " Escapism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78169,
    "questionText": " The system which is observed to do progress or reform",
    "answerText": " Reformism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78170,
    "questionText": " Temple dedicated to all the gods",
    "answerText": " Pantheon"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78171,
    "questionText": " Talk that brings bad reputation to somebody",
    "answerText": " Scandal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78172,
    "questionText": " The study of population",
    "answerText": " Demography"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78173,
    "questionText": " The study of physical phenomenon of lakes",
    "answerText": " Limnology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78174,
    "questionText": " Spreading by infection",
    "answerText": " Infectious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78175,
    "questionText": " Specialist in mental or emotional disturbance",
    "answerText": " Psychiatrist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78176,
    "questionText": " Speak in a very low tone",
    "answerText": " Whisper"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78177,
    "questionText": " Something that is hidden",
    "answerText": " Mystery"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78178,
    "questionText": " Somebody that foretells the coming of something",
    "answerText": " Harbinger"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78179,
    "questionText": " Soldiers on big guns mounted on wheels",
    "answerText": " Artillery"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78180,
    "questionText": " So deep that the bottom cannot be reached",
    "answerText": " Unfathomable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78181,
    "questionText": " A small shop that sells fashionable clothes, cosmetics etc",
    "answerText": " Boutique"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78182,
    "questionText": " Shamelessly rude",
    "answerText": " Impudent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78183,
    "questionText": " Serious crime like murder, arson",
    "answerText": " Felony"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78184,
    "questionText": " Send rays of light or heat",
    "answerText": " Radiate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78185,
    "questionText": " Send back a criminal into custody for further investigation",
    "answerText": " Remand"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78186,
    "questionText": " Secret place difficult to access",
    "answerText": " Recess"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78187,
    "questionText": " Secret agreement for a fraudulent purpose",
    "answerText": " Collusion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78188,
    "questionText": " Search in the dark",
    "answerText": " Grope / Fumble"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78189,
    "questionText": " Search for something",
    "answerText": " Quest"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78190,
    "questionText": " Secret religious meeting",
    "answerText": " Conventicle"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78191,
    "questionText": " Sea with a group of many islands",
    "answerText": " Archipelago"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78192,
    "questionText": " A signature on the back of a paper or cheque",
    "answerText": " Endorsement"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78193,
    "questionText": " Showing contemptuous indifference",
    "answerText": " Supercilious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78194,
    "questionText": " A short summary of a book or speech",
    "answerText": " Epitome"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78195,
    "questionText": " Signal under martial law for people to remain indoors.",
    "answerText": " Curfew"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78196,
    "questionText": " Showing deep sorrow for wrong doing",
    "answerText": " Contrite"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78197,
    "questionText": " A short saying or poem which express an idea in a very clever and amusing way",
    "answerText": " Epigram"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78198,
    "questionText": " A short journey for pleasure",
    "answerText": " Excursion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78199,
    "questionText": " A short expression of general truth"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78200,
    "questionText": " A short amusing story about some real person or event",
    "answerText": " Anecdote"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78201,
    "questionText": " Scornful and contemptuous language",
    "answerText": " Opprobrium"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78202,
    "questionText": " Science of weight",
    "answerText": " Metrology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78203,
    "questionText": " Science of time",
    "answerText": " Horology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78204,
    "questionText": " Science of writing and compiling a dictionary",
    "answerText": " Lexicography"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78205,
    "questionText": " Science of the races of mankind and their relation to one another",
    "answerText": " Ethnology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78206,
    "questionText": " Science of the physical structure of the body",
    "answerText": " Anatomy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78207,
    "questionText": " Science of the habits of living things in relation to their environment",
    "answerText": " Ecology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78208,
    "questionText": " Science of the constitution of the whole universe",
    "answerText": " Cosmography"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78209,
    "questionText": " Science of the causes of diseases",
    "answerText": " Etiology/Aetiology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78210,
    "questionText": " Science of mankind as an animal",
    "answerText": " Anthropology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78211,
    "questionText": " Science of mechanical and industrial arts",
    "answerText": " Technology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78212,
    "questionText": " Science of healthy living",
    "answerText": " Hygiene"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78213,
    "questionText": " Science of inscriptions",
    "answerText": " Epigraphy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78214,
    "questionText": " Science dealing with the proper use of terms",
    "answerText": " Terminology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78215,
    "questionText": " Science dealing with heredity",
    "answerText": " Genetics"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78216,
    "questionText": " Science and technology of metals",
    "answerText": " Metallurgy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78217,
    "questionText": " Science and philosophy of human law",
    "answerText": " Jurisprudence"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78218,
    "questionText": " Science and art of preparing and making good food",
    "answerText": " Gastronomy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78219,
    "questionText": " The designing, building and flying of aircraft",
    "answerText": " Aviation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78220,
    "questionText": " School for very young children",
    "answerText": " Kindergarten"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78221,
    "questionText": " Say in advance what is likely to happen",
    "answerText": " Forecast/predict/Foretell"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78222,
    "questionText": " Say aloud from memory",
    "answerText": " Recite"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78223,
    "questionText": " Saving of property from loss by fire",
    "answerText": " Salvage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78224,
    "questionText": " Salt water lake separated from the sea by sand banks",
    "answerText": " Lagoon"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78225,
    "questionText": " Rules for formal behaviour among people",
    "answerText": " Etiquette"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78226,
    "questionText": " Room for washing kitchen utensils",
    "answerText": " Scullery"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78227,
    "questionText": " Roof supported by columns at the entrance of a building",
    "answerText": " Portico / Porch"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78228,
    "questionText": " Ritual washing of the body",
    "answerText": " Ablution"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78229,
    "questionText": " Rising in arms against an establishment/ government.",
    "answerText": " Insurrection/Rebellion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78230,
    "questionText": " Resulting in death or ending in disaster",
    "answerText": " Fatal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78231,
    "questionText": " Relation between different aspects of a thing.",
    "answerText": " Perspective"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78232,
    "questionText": " Reasoning power of the mind",
    "answerText": " Intellect"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78233,
    "questionText": " Receiving guests warmly",
    "answerText": " Hospitality"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78234,
    "questionText": " Record of events in the order of their happenings.",
    "answerText": " Chronicle"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78235,
    "questionText": " To raise a pattern or design on the surface of something.",
    "answerText": " Emboss"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78236,
    "questionText": " Quick to judge and understand",
    "answerText": " Perspicacious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78237,
    "questionText": " Question or problem difficult to answer or understand.",
    "answerText": " Puzzle/Riddle/Enigma"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78238,
    "questionText": " Put under the surface of water",
    "answerText": " Submerge"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78239,
    "questionText": " Put off for a future time",
    "answerText": " Postpone/ procrastinate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78240,
    "questionText": " Put into the form of a code",
    "answerText": " Codify"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78241,
    "questionText": " Pull out of usual shape",
    "answerText": " Distort"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78242,
    "questionText": " Property inherited from one's father",
    "answerText": " Patrimony"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78243,
    "questionText": " Producing a lot of books or other things",
    "answerText": " Prolific"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78244,
    "questionText": " Process of sewing designs on cloth or other materials.",
    "answerText": " Embroidery"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78245,
    "questionText": " Principle that the war should and could be abolished.",
    "answerText": " Pacifism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78246,
    "questionText": " Handwriting that can be easily read",
    "answerText": " Legible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78247,
    "questionText": " Happening at the same time",
    "answerText": " Contemporary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78248,
    "questionText": " Government run by a dictator",
    "answerText": " Dictatorship"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78249,
    "questionText": " Government by person of highest social order.",
    "answerText": " Aristocracy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78250,
    "questionText": " Government by intelligentsia",
    "answerText": " Meritocracy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78251,
    "questionText": " Government by the rich and the powerful class",
    "answerText": " Plutocracy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78252,
    "questionText": " Government by officials",
    "answerText": " Bureaucracy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78253,
    "questionText": " Government by elected representatives",
    "answerText": " Democracy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78254,
    "questionText": " Government by elected representatives without a monarch",
    "answerText": " Republic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78255,
    "questionText": " Hater of marriage",
    "answerText": " Misogamist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78256,
    "questionText": " Having more than one meaning",
    "answerText": " Ambiguous / Equivocal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78257,
    "questionText": " Imaginary ailments (disease)",
    "answerText": " Hypochondria"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78258,
    "questionText": " Offering made to God",
    "answerText": " Oblation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78259,
    "questionText": " An official agreement to a proposal",
    "answerText": " Assent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78260,
    "questionText": " Gathering of all things",
    "answerText": " Omnibus"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78261,
    "questionText": " An official announcement issued to the press",
    "answerText": " Communique"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78262,
    "questionText": " An official counting of the population",
    "answerText": " Census"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78263,
    "questionText": " One who analyses handwriting",
    "answerText": " Graphologist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78264,
    "questionText": " One who attacks",
    "answerText": " Assaulter/ Assailant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78265,
    "questionText": " One who believes that nothing can be said about God",
    "answerText": " Agnostic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78266,
    "questionText": " One who can neither read nor write",
    "answerText": " Illiterate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78267,
    "questionText": " One who cannot be corrected",
    "answerText": " Incorrigible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78268,
    "questionText": " For warning of an impending danger",
    "answerText": " Premonition"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78269,
    "questionText": " Fixed sum of money paid to somebody as income in his life time",
    "answerText": " Annuity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78270,
    "questionText": " Fit for bad temper or anger",
    "answerText": " Tantrum"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78271,
    "questionText": " Fear of foreigners",
    "answerText": " Xenophobia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78272,
    "questionText": " Fear of oneself",
    "answerText": " Autophoby"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78273,
    "questionText": " Refreshment or amusement after hard work",
    "answerText": " Recreation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78274,
    "questionText": " Animals with four feet",
    "answerText": " Quadruped"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78275,
    "questionText": " Any soft drink except water",
    "answerText": " Beverage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78276,
    "questionText": " Art of growing vegetables, fruits, flowers.",
    "answerText": " Horticulture"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78277,
    "questionText": " Art of making fireworks",
    "answerText": " Pyrotechnics"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78278,
    "questionText": " Art of map making",
    "answerText": " Cartography"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78279,
    "questionText": " Style of speaking well",
    "answerText": " Elocution"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78280,
    "questionText": " Artificial centre for honey bees",
    "answerText": " Hive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78281,
    "questionText": " Assembly of worshippers",
    "answerText": " Congregation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78282,
    "questionText": " Author's explanatory remarks at the beginning of a book.",
    "answerText": " Preface"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78283,
    "questionText": " Distinguishing marks of an office",
    "answerText": " Insignia / Badge"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78284,
    "questionText": " A bed of a new born baby",
    "answerText": " Cradle/Crib"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78285,
    "questionText": " Belief not based on reason or knowledge.",
    "answerText": " Superstition"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78286,
    "questionText": " Bird that comes and goes with seasons",
    "answerText": " Migratory"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78287,
    "questionText": " Blessing given by a priest",
    "answerText": " Benediction"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78288,
    "questionText": " Board of directors in a company or organization",
    "answerText": " Directorate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78289,
    "questionText": " A body of delegates",
    "answerText": " Delegacy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78290,
    "questionText": " A book of a sacred/religious nature",
    "answerText": " Scripture"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78291,
    "questionText": " Books, pictures etc intended to arouse sexual desire",
    "answerText": " Erotica"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78292,
    "questionText": " Brief account of a subject",
    "answerText": " Summary/compendium"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78293,
    "questionText": " Break an agreement, law or promise",
    "answerText": " Violate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78294,
    "questionText": " A building where military weapons are prepared or stored.",
    "answerText": " Arsenal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78295,
    "questionText": " That can live without outside help",
    "answerText": " Viable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78296,
    "questionText": " A caretaker of a public building",
    "answerText": " Custodian"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78297,
    "questionText": " Attachment to what is natural",
    "answerText": " Naturalism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78298,
    "questionText": " Approximate calculation of something",
    "answerText": " Estimate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78299,
    "questionText": " Change to something abnormal, unnatural",
    "answerText": " Perversion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78300,
    "questionText": " Child of unusual or remarkable talent",
    "answerText": " Prodigy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78301,
    "questionText": " Chief actor or character in a story or drama.",
    "answerText": " Protagonist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78302,
    "questionText": " Habitual character and disposition",
    "answerText": " Ethos"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78303,
    "questionText": " Using of new words",
    "answerText": " Neologism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78304,
    "questionText": " One who holds that nothing is or can be known of the existence of God",
    "answerText": " Agnostic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78305,
    "questionText": " To destroy completely",
    "answerText": " Annihilate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78306,
    "questionText": " That which is open to more than one interpretation",
    "answerText": " Ambiguous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78307,
    "questionText": " Capable of living both on land and water",
    "answerText": " Amphibious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78308,
    "questionText": " In a state of mutual hostility",
    "answerText": " Antagonistic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78309,
    "questionText": " Neutral party called upon to settle a dispute without reference to any other party",
    "answerText": " Arbiter"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78310,
    "questionText": " A government by one man",
    "answerText": " Autocracy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78311,
    "questionText": " A narrative describing one subject under the guise of another or a sustained metaphor",
    "answerText": " Allegory"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78312,
    "questionText": " Kind of substance in the blood tending to neutralise others that are harmful",
    "answerText": " Antibody"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78313,
    "questionText": " The science of bee keeping cultivation and maintenance of bee-hives",
    "answerText": " Apiculture"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78314,
    "questionText": " Recurrence of some disease after generation or similarity in special features with remote ancestors",
    "answerText": " Atavism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78315,
    "questionText": " To mitigate or lessen the suffering or pain",
    "answerText": " Alleviate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78316,
    "questionText": " A positive and emphatic advancement of change or statement against a person",
    "answerText": " Allegation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78317,
    "questionText": " One who has regard for others as the basic principle of his actions",
    "answerText": " Altruistic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78318,
    "questionText": " A person guilty of setting fire to the property",
    "answerText": " Arsonist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78319,
    "questionText": " Sensitiveness to the action of a particular food",
    "answerText": " Allergy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78320,
    "questionText": " To make better, to improve or to lift to a better place",
    "answerText": " Ameliorate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78321,
    "questionText": " By which human form and personality is attributed to God",
    "answerText": " Anthropomorphism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78322,
    "questionText": " A cessation of active use of arms signifying a short period of truce",
    "answerText": " Armistice"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78323,
    "questionText": " A mistake in the chronological order or a thing which is out of harmony with a period",
    "answerText": " Anachronism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78324,
    "questionText": " A mechanic or craftsman who has acquired skill in a particular craft",
    "answerText": " Artisan"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78325,
    "questionText": " A man who is a great lover of books",
    "answerText": " Bibliophile"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78326,
    "questionText": " The state of having two wives",
    "answerText": " Bigamy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78327,
    "questionText": " Belonging to a class between the gentry and the labourers",
    "answerText": " Bourgeois"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78328,
    "questionText": " Socially unconventional, a man of free and easy habits",
    "answerText": " Bohemian"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78329,
    "questionText": " One who readily believes everything and everyone",
    "answerText": " Credulous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78330,
    "questionText": " A citizen of the world",
    "answerText": " Cosmopolitan"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78331,
    "questionText": " A man who is recovering from an illness.",
    "answerText": " Convalescent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78332,
    "questionText": " The state of being without a wife; abstaining from marital relationship",
    "answerText": " Celibacy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78333,
    "questionText": " Centre of attraction or interest",
    "answerText": " Cynosure"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78334,
    "questionText": " A person who really understands the value of art, antiques etc",
    "answerText": " Connoisseur"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78335,
    "questionText": " Hundred in Anniversary",
    "answerText": " Centenary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78336,
    "questionText": " Any language in speaking only",
    "answerText": " Colloquialism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78337,
    "questionText": " To seize by authority",
    "answerText": " Confiscate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78338,
    "questionText": " To give someone something to make good for loss or damage",
    "answerText": " Compensate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78339,
    "questionText": " Reaching the final or the highest point",
    "answerText": " Consummation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78340,
    "questionText": " A man who has lots of investments in the private sector",
    "answerText": " Capitalist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78341,
    "questionText": " A ruler or boss who uses force in order to make people obey him",
    "answerText": " Dictator"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78342,
    "questionText": " One who is engaged in the diplomatic service of a country",
    "answerText": " Diplomat"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78343,
    "questionText": " Nature of double dealing",
    "answerText": " Duplicity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78344,
    "questionText": " A person who fails in the performance of his duty or commits an offence",
    "answerText": " Deliquent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78345,
    "questionText": " Fruit or sweet-dish usually eaten after the main meals",
    "answerText": " Dessert"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78346,
    "questionText": " A dabbler in the arts and literature",
    "answerText": " Dilettante"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78347,
    "questionText": " The state of being miserable bereft of all material possessions",
    "answerText": " Destitution"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78348,
    "questionText": " A democratic orator",
    "answerText": " Demagogue"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78349,
    "questionText": " The inability of a person to shun alcoholic drinks",
    "answerText": " Dipsomania"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78350,
    "questionText": " Something regularly found among a particular people or community",
    "answerText": " Endemic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78351,
    "questionText": " A person who likes to indulge in refined sensuous pleasure",
    "answerText": " Epicure"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78352,
    "questionText": " To remove all traces of",
    "answerText": " Eradicate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78353,
    "questionText": " A professor who has retired from service",
    "answerText": " Emeritus"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78354,
    "questionText": " An unusual bent of mind",
    "answerText": " Eccentricity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78355,
    "questionText": " One who is always seeking to escape from the harsh realities of life",
    "answerText": " Escapist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78356,
    "questionText": " To quicken the completion of work",
    "answerText": " Expedite"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78357,
    "questionText": " To free from the confines of something to liberate from",
    "answerText": " Emancipate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78358,
    "questionText": " A short but pithy and weightily saying, a short witty phrase",
    "answerText": " Epigram"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78359,
    "questionText": " Substitution of a mild for a very blunt expression",
    "answerText": " Euphemism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78360,
    "questionText": " That which is all inclusive",
    "answerText": " Exhaustive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78361,
    "questionText": " Not refined and fluent but full of jerky movements.",
    "answerText": " Erratic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78362,
    "questionText": " That which tries to side-track the main issue by irrelevance",
    "answerText": " Evasive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78363,
    "questionText": " A state of mental weariness form of occupation.",
    "answerText": " Ennui"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78364,
    "questionText": " To make atonement for one's sins",
    "answerText": " Expiate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78365,
    "questionText": " Words or phrases inscribed on a person's tomb",
    "answerText": " Epitaph"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78366,
    "questionText": " A person authorised to execute a legal deed",
    "answerText": " Executor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78367,
    "questionText": " One who is subject to failure or to committing mistakes",
    "answerText": " Fallible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78368,
    "questionText": " The animals of a particular region or epoch",
    "answerText": " Fauna"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78369,
    "questionText": " A man who is genuinely interested in the welfare and emancipation of women",
    "answerText": " Feminist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78370,
    "questionText": " A man with narrow and prejudiced religious views",
    "answerText": " Fanatic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78371,
    "questionText": " One who cannot be easily pleased",
    "answerText": " Fastidious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78372,
    "questionText": " Something artificial having the appearance of something got up",
    "answerText": " Factitious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78373,
    "questionText": " As opposed to realistic, imagined not real",
    "answerText": " Fictitious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78374,
    "questionText": " Extremely showy and colourful personality; valuable and verbose speech",
    "answerText": " Flamboyant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78375,
    "questionText": " Tendency to grow downwards",
    "answerText": " Geotropism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78376,
    "questionText": " Act of killing one's clan, family or community",
    "answerText": " Genocide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78377,
    "questionText": " A connoisseur of wines and table delicacies.",
    "answerText": " Gourmet"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78378,
    "questionText": " The act of killing a human being",
    "answerText": " Homicide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78379,
    "questionText": " Traits, mental or physical, received from forefathers by birth",
    "answerText": " Hereditary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78380,
    "questionText": " One who lives in seclusion with thoughts of God",
    "answerText": " Hermit"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78381,
    "questionText": " Voluntary fees paid for professional services which carry no salary",
    "answerText": " Honorarium"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78382,
    "questionText": " One who expresses ideas which are not in keeping with conventional religious teaching",
    "answerText": " Heretic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78383,
    "questionText": " One who is not orthodox",
    "answerText": " Heterodox"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78384,
    "questionText": " One who generously acts for the welfare and amelioration of mankind",
    "answerText": " Humanitarian"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78385,
    "questionText": " A gesture of respect and devotion",
    "answerText": " Homage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78386,
    "questionText": " Rhetorical exaggeration in speaking or in a piece of writing",
    "answerText": " Hyperbole"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78387,
    "questionText": " A person who pretends to be what he is not, a pretender",
    "answerText": " Hypocrite"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78388,
    "questionText": " That which cannot be broken through",
    "answerText": " Impregnable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78389,
    "questionText": " That which can be easily understood",
    "answerText": " Intelligible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78390,
    "questionText": " That which is most likely to happen in future.",
    "answerText": " Imminent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78391,
    "questionText": " One who cannot be soothed or calmed or near pacified",
    "answerText": " Implacable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78392,
    "questionText": " That which cannot be put into practice",
    "answerText": " Impracticable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78393,
    "questionText": " One who cannot be corrected or reformed.",
    "answerText": " Incorrigible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78394,
    "questionText": " To accuse or charge a person with a crime in due form of law",
    "answerText": " Indict"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78395,
    "questionText": " That which cannot be easily imitated or copied",
    "answerText": " Inimitable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78396,
    "questionText": " That which cannot be defeated",
    "answerText": " Invincible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78397,
    "questionText": " A personal peculiarity of temperament or constitution",
    "answerText": " Idiosyncrasy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78398,
    "questionText": " A man who is easily irritated and loses temper",
    "answerText": " Irritable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78399,
    "questionText": " A disease in which a man suffers from sleeplessness",
    "answerText": " Insomnia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78400,
    "questionText": " A country or a people or community which is in open revolt or rebellion",
    "answerText": " Insurgent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78401,
    "questionText": " A man who has a most uncompromising attitude especially in politics",
    "answerText": " Intransigent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78402,
    "questionText": " Ascribing or attributing to something or someone",
    "answerText": " Imputation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78403,
    "questionText": " A decision which cannot be changed or modified",
    "answerText": " Irrevocable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78404,
    "questionText": " Produced or manufactured within the country without foreign aid or collaboration",
    "answerText": " Indigenous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78405,
    "questionText": " A deceptive appearance, statement or belief",
    "answerText": " Illusion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78406,
    "questionText": " .Use of language or gesture which implies threat to someone",
    "answerText": " Intimidation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78407,
    "questionText": " The act of provoking and goading a man",
    "answerText": " Instigation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78408,
    "questionText": " Something which provides interest and attraction.",
    "answerText": " Incentive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78409,
    "questionText": " A subtle allusive and generally deprecatory remark",
    "answerText": " Innuendo"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78410,
    "questionText": " Something that is too delightful or beautiful for words",
    "answerText": " Ineffable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78411,
    "questionText": " A man who has no money",
    "answerText": " Impecunious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78412,
    "questionText": " III timed circumstances",
    "answerText": " Irony"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78413,
    "questionText": " A person who is well versed in law",
    "answerText": " Jurist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78414,
    "questionText": " An excessively morbid desire to steal",
    "answerText": " Kleptomania"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78415,
    "questionText": " Technical knowledge of a particular work.",
    "answerText": " Know-how"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78416,
    "questionText": " Extremely extravagant in manners and morals.",
    "answerText": " Licentious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78417,
    "questionText": " A hater of mankind",
    "answerText": " Misanthrope"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78418,
    "questionText": " A hater of women",
    "answerText": " Misogynist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78419,
    "questionText": " A person who believes in being married to one person at a time Or, A man who has only one wife",
    "answerText": " Monogamist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78420,
    "questionText": " Belonging to this world, earthly",
    "answerText": " Mundane"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78421,
    "questionText": " Application of name or descriptive term to an object to which it is not literally applicable",
    "answerText": " Metaphor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78422,
    "questionText": " A scene or situation which is gruesomely imaginative or full of gruesome details",
    "answerText": " Macabre"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78423,
    "questionText": " One who plays the role of bringing two antagonistic parties together",
    "answerText": " Mediator"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78424,
    "questionText": " A change that befalls something",
    "answerText": " Mutation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78425,
    "questionText": " A drama which is marked by very crude appeal to feelings and emotions",
    "answerText": " Melodrama"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78426,
    "questionText": " One who believes in the philosophy that nothing has real existence",
    "answerText": " Nihilist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78427,
    "questionText": " .A quick remedy or apartent medicine or similarly a pet scheme",
    "answerText": " Nostrum"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78428,
    "questionText": " Science and study that treats of coins as medals",
    "answerText": " Numismatics"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78429,
    "questionText": " Extremely loud and showy as opposed to reserved and modest",
    "answerText": " Ostentatious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78430,
    "questionText": " To banish or turn out of society and fellowship",
    "answerText": " Ostracise"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78431,
    "questionText": " The art of spelling words correctly",
    "answerText": " Orthography"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78432,
    "questionText": " An unscrupulous person, who puts experience before principle",
    "answerText": " Opportunist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78433,
    "questionText": " The act of fixing of a proper position for something",
    "answerText": " Orientation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78434,
    "questionText": " The science of languages",
    "answerText": " Philology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78435,
    "questionText": " Science dealing with stamp-collection",
    "answerText": " Philately"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78436,
    "questionText": " Science of vocal natural sounds",
    "answerText": " Phonology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78437,
    "questionText": " Tomake evasive or misleading statements.",
    "answerText": " Prevaricate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78438,
    "questionText": " Statement showing remarkable degree of prediction",
    "answerText": " Prophecy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78439,
    "questionText": " Study of ancient writings and inscriptions.",
    "answerText": " Palaeography"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78440,
    "questionText": " A passage marking the close of a speech",
    "answerText": " Peroration"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78441,
    "questionText": " A man who practises psychiatry",
    "answerText": " Psychiatrist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78442,
    "questionText": " A school teacher or a man affecting learning",
    "answerText": " Pedagogue"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78443,
    "questionText": " Some previous example from the past",
    "answerText": " Precedent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78444,
    "questionText": " A child born after the death of his father",
    "answerText": " Posthumous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78445,
    "questionText": " A book published after the death of its author",
    "answerText": " Posthumous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78446,
    "questionText": " One who makes love now to one and now to another",
    "answerText": " Philanderer"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78447,
    "questionText": " Original model",
    "answerText": " Prototype"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78448,
    "questionText": " Application of pasteurism in order to sterilize milk etc by exposure to high temperature",
    "answerText": " Pasteurisation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78449,
    "questionText": " Former holder of an office or a position",
    "answerText": " Predecessor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78450,
    "questionText": " To restore to good condition",
    "answerText": " Rehabilitation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78451,
    "questionText": " A person who refuses compliance with",
    "answerText": " Recalcitrant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78452,
    "questionText": " That which reminds one of something",
    "answerText": " Reminiscent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78453,
    "questionText": " A reasoner willing to avail himself of fallacies that will help his case",
    "answerText": " Sophist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78454,
    "questionText": " A very delicate flaw or mistake which is not expected from the person making it",
    "answerText": " Solecism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78455,
    "questionText": " A symbolic religious ceremony especially baptism",
    "answerText": " Sacrament"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78456,
    "questionText": " Someone on whom the blame for other's sins can be fixed",
    "answerText": " Scapegoat"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78457,
    "questionText": " Abounding in blood",
    "answerText": " Sanguine"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78458,
    "questionText": " Over bearing",
    "answerText": " Supercilious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78459,
    "questionText": " Extremely refined in dress, conduct and speech; Fashionable and modernised.",
    "answerText": " Sophisticated"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78460,
    "questionText": " A person who flatters others for personal motives",
    "answerText": " Sycophant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78461,
    "questionText": " Affectedly and pompously formal person or style",
    "answerText": " Sententious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78462,
    "questionText": " One who takes pleasure in cruel, inhuman and unnatural acts of tyranny",
    "answerText": " Sadist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78463,
    "questionText": " That which surpasses",
    "answerText": " Transcendental"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78464,
    "questionText": " Communication between mind and other than the known channel of senses",
    "answerText": " Telepathy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78465,
    "questionText": " The practice of taking exorbitant or excessive interest on the money lent",
    "answerText": " Usury"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78466,
    "questionText": " Guilty of accepting bribes extremely mercenary.",
    "answerText": " Venal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78467,
    "questionText": " Extreme enthusiasm for a cause",
    "answerText": " Zeal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78468,
    "questionText": " A person who is indifferent to pleasure or pain",
    "answerText": " Stoic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78469,
    "questionText": " A person sent to a mission",
    "answerText": " Emissary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78470,
    "questionText": " A person who spends his money recklessly",
    "answerText": " Spendthrift"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78471,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being penetrated",
    "answerText": " Impenetrable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78472,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being wound or hurt",
    "answerText": " Invulnerable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78473,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being repaired",
    "answerText": " Irreparable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78474,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being avoided",
    "answerText": " Unavoidable / inevitable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78475,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being explained or accounted for",
    "answerText": " Inexplicable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78476,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being expressed in words",
    "answerText": " Inexpressible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78477,
    "questionText": " Not definitely or clearly expressed",
    "answerText": " Inexplicity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78478,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being justified or excused",
    "answerText": " Inexcusable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78479,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being solved",
    "answerText": " Insoluble"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78480,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being defended",
    "answerText": " Indefensible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78481,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being taken by force of arms",
    "answerText": " Impregnable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78482,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being admitted or allowed",
    "answerText": " Inadmissible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78483,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being reached",
    "answerText": " Inaccessible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78484,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being tired out",
    "answerText": " Inexhaustible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78485,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being perceived by the senses",
    "answerText": " Imperceptible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78486,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being destroyed",
    "answerText": " Indestructible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78487,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being divided",
    "answerText": " Indivisible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78488,
    "questionText": " Liable to be easily broken",
    "answerText": " Brittle"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78489,
    "questionText": " An assembly of worshippers",
    "answerText": " Congregatio"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78490,
    "questionText": " Occurring at the same time",
    "answerText": " Simultaneous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78491,
    "questionText": " Allowing the passage of rays of light",
    "answerText": " Transparent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78492,
    "questionText": " Not allowing the passage of light",
    "answerText": " Opaque"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78493,
    "questionText": " Of unknown or unadmitted authorship",
    "answerText": " Anonymous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78494,
    "questionText": " Compulsory enlistment for military and other services",
    "answerText": " Conscription"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78495,
    "questionText": " A figure with many angles or sides",
    "answerText": " Polygon"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78496,
    "questionText": " Belonging to all parts of the world",
    "answerText": " Universal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78497,
    "questionText": " The science of reasoning",
    "answerText": " Logic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78498,
    "questionText": " The cessation of warfare before a treaty is signed",
    "answerText": " Armistice"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78499,
    "questionText": " Signature of someone's name without his permission",
    "answerText": " Forgery"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78500,
    "questionText": " Property inherited from one's father or ancestors",
    "answerText": " Patrimony"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78501,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being out into practice",
    "answerText": " Impracticable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78502,
    "questionText": " Incapable of being overcome",
    "answerText": " Insurmountable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78503,
    "questionText": " Having no beginning or end to its existence",
    "answerText": " Eternal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78504,
    "questionText": " His motive was merely to get money",
    "answerText": " Mercenary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78505,
    "questionText": " Forbidden, prohibited by law",
    "answerText": " Illicit"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78506,
    "questionText": " Fond of entertaining guests",
    "answerText": " Hospitable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78507,
    "questionText": " A general pardon of political offenders",
    "answerText": " Amnesty"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78508,
    "questionText": " Objects possessed of life",
    "answerText": " Animate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78509,
    "questionText": " Persons who work in the same department of an office",
    "answerText": " Colleagues"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78510,
    "questionText": " A place where people lunch on payment",
    "answerText": " Restaurant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78511,
    "questionText": " A place with a good climate for invalids",
    "answerText": " Sanatorium"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78512,
    "questionText": " Government in which no distinction is made between persons of different religions",
    "answerText": " Secular"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78513,
    "questionText": " One who is qualified to navigate an aircraft.",
    "answerText": " Navigator"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78514,
    "questionText": " To increase the gravity of an offence or the intensity of a dispute",
    "answerText": " Aggravate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78515,
    "questionText": " To increase the speed of",
    "answerText": " Accelerate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78516,
    "questionText": " Allowance due to a wife from her husband on separation",
    "answerText": " Alimony"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78517,
    "questionText": " The act of talking impiously about sacred things",
    "answerText": " Blasphemy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78518,
    "questionText": " A man or woman with skin and hair of auburn colour",
    "answerText": " Blonde"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78519,
    "questionText": " Willful and persistent resistance to lawful authority",
    "answerText": " Contumacy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78520,
    "questionText": " To restrain by force or impel a person by force.",
    "answerText": " Coerce"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78521,
    "questionText": " Belonging or pertaining to an individual from birth",
    "answerText": " Congenital"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78522,
    "questionText": " Eater of flesh",
    "answerText": " Carnivore"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78523,
    "questionText": " Income just sufficient to live on",
    "answerText": " Subsistence"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78524,
    "questionText": " A person who is insensible to kind thoughts or sympathetic feelings",
    "answerText": " Callous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78525,
    "questionText": " One who prescribes medicine",
    "answerText": " Physician"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78526,
    "questionText": " Total loss of voice",
    "answerText": " Aphonia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78527,
    "questionText": " To do away with a rule",
    "answerText": " Abrogate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78528,
    "questionText": " To make thin or fine or to reduce the strength.",
    "answerText": " Attentuate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78529,
    "questionText": " Deviation from the common rule or standard.",
    "answerText": " Anomaly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78530,
    "questionText": " A person who starves the body for the good of the soul",
    "answerText": " Ascetic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78531,
    "questionText": " Animals equally at home on land or at sea.",
    "answerText": " Amphibian"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78532,
    "questionText": " Stealthily done",
    "answerText": " Surreptitious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78533,
    "questionText": " One not concerned with right or wrong",
    "answerText": " Amoral"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78534,
    "questionText": " A person who opposes war or use of military",
    "answerText": " Pacifist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78535,
    "questionText": " Severely abusive writing in journals",
    "answerText": " Scurrilous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78536,
    "questionText": " Call upon God or any other power (like law) etc for help or protection",
    "answerText": " Invocation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78537,
    "questionText": " Fear of being enclosed in a small closed space",
    "answerText": " Claustrophobia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78538,
    "questionText": " Fear of crowds",
    "answerText": " Agoraphobia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78539,
    "questionText": " Fear of strangers",
    "answerText": " Xenophobia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78540,
    "questionText": " Mental derangement",
    "answerText": " Paranoia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78541,
    "questionText": " Succession of rulers belonging to one family",
    "answerText": " Dynasty"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78542,
    "questionText": " To cut something into two pieces",
    "answerText": " Sever"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78543,
    "questionText": " Flat metal or porcelain plate fixed on a wall as an ornament or memorial",
    "answerText": " Plaque"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78544,
    "questionText": " Act of deceiving somebody in order to make money",
    "answerText": " Fraud"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78545,
    "questionText": " Ashort poem or speech addressed to the spectators after the conclusion of a drama",
    "answerText": " Epilogue"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78546,
    "questionText": " Capable of being understood in either of two or more possible senses and therefore not definite.",
    "answerText": " Ambiguous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78547,
    "questionText": " Something capable of being done",
    "answerText": " Feasible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78548,
    "questionText": " One who walks on ropes",
    "answerText": " Acrobat"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78549,
    "questionText": " The study of the origin and history of words",
    "answerText": " Etymology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78550,
    "questionText": " The study of maps",
    "answerText": " Cartography"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78551,
    "questionText": " Tough tissues in joints",
    "answerText": " Ligaments"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78552,
    "questionText": " Building in which dead bodies are kept for a time",
    "answerText": " Mortuary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78553,
    "questionText": " or, A place for keeping dead bodies before burial or cremation",
    "answerText": " Mortuary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78554,
    "questionText": " Clinic for the treatment for consumptives in hilly areas where the climate is salubrious",
    "answerText": " Sanatorium"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78555,
    "questionText": " One who believes that gaining pleasure is the most important thing in life",
    "answerText": " Hedonist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78556,
    "questionText": " A person who has no understanding for arts / uncivilized person",
    "answerText": " Philistine"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78557,
    "questionText": " One who breaks the established traditions and image",
    "answerText": " Iconoclast"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78558,
    "questionText": " A person having deep study in a language",
    "answerText": " Philologist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78559,
    "questionText": " One who resists to the end",
    "answerText": " Diehard"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78560,
    "questionText": " Wild and noisy disorder",
    "answerText": " Pandemonium"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78561,
    "questionText": " Diehard, believer and supporter of some religion, cause or political ideology",
    "answerText": " Fanatic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78562,
    "questionText": " Property handed down after the death of a person",
    "answerText": " Legacy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78563,
    "questionText": " or Property that which is given to a person by one's will",
    "answerText": " Legacy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78564,
    "questionText": " Placing a thing beside another",
    "answerText": " Juxtapose"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78565,
    "questionText": " Expert in the scientific study of skin diseases",
    "answerText": " Dermatologist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78566,
    "questionText": " Of very bad morals; characterised by debasement or degeneration",
    "answerText": " Depraved"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78567,
    "questionText": " Body of human being or animal enabled for burial",
    "answerText": " Mummy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78568,
    "questionText": " The abandonment of one's country or cause.",
    "answerText": " Desertion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78569,
    "questionText": " Treatment by means of exercise and massage",
    "answerText": " Physiotherapy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78570,
    "questionText": " Bitter and violent attack in words",
    "answerText": " Diatribe"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78571,
    "questionText": " To be biased against",
    "answerText": " Prejudiced"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78572,
    "questionText": " To examine one's own thoughts and feelings",
    "answerText": " Introspection"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78573,
    "questionText": " A small enclosure for cattle, sheep, poultry etc",
    "answerText": " Fold"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78574,
    "questionText": " Large scale departure of people",
    "answerText": " Exodus"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78575,
    "questionText": " A sudden rush of wind",
    "answerText": " storm"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78576,
    "questionText": " A man of odd habits",
    "answerText": " Eccentric"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78577,
    "questionText": " Lack of enough blood in the body",
    "answerText": " Anaemia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78578,
    "questionText": " Mania for stealing articles",
    "answerText": " Kleptomania"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78579,
    "questionText": " A child of unusual or remarkable talent",
    "answerText": " Precocious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78580,
    "questionText": " Belief that God is in everything and that everything is God",
    "answerText": " Pantheism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78581,
    "questionText": " The state of being miserable, bereft of all possessions",
    "answerText": " Destitute"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78582,
    "questionText": " That which cannot be called back",
    "answerText": " Irredeemable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78583,
    "questionText": " One who journeys from place to place",
    "answerText": " Itinerant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78584,
    "questionText": " Commencement of adjacent words with the same letter",
    "answerText": " Alliteration"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78585,
    "questionText": " A specialist who tests eyesight",
    "answerText": " Ophthalmologist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78586,
    "questionText": " A wall built to prevent the sea or a river from flooding an area",
    "answerText": " Embankment"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78587,
    "questionText": " Something that is poisonous or unhealthy",
    "answerText": " Trivial"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78588,
    "questionText": " A mental illness or condition in which somebody has an exaggerated belief in their own importance or power",
    "answerText": " Megalomania"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78589,
    "questionText": " A person who is inactive",
    "answerText": " Torpid"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78590,
    "questionText": " Relating to tragedy",
    "answerText": " Tragic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78591,
    "questionText": " Loss of memory",
    "answerText": " Amnesia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78592,
    "questionText": " A small umbrella",
    "answerText": " Parasol"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78593,
    "questionText": " An insatiable, often periodic, craving for alcoholic drink",
    "answerText": " Dipsomania"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78594,
    "questionText": " A mental illness that causes a strong desire to set fire to things",
    "answerText": " Pyromania"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78595,
    "questionText": " An infectious disease in back of the throat.",
    "answerText": " Diphtheria"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78596,
    "questionText": " Criticising popular beliefs or established customs and ideas",
    "answerText": " Iconoclastic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78597,
    "questionText": " A place where government / public records are kept",
    "answerText": " Archive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78598,
    "questionText": " The practice of worshipping statues as gods",
    "answerText": " Idolatry"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78599,
    "questionText": " Living together of a man and woman without being married to each other",
    "answerText": " Concubinage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78600,
    "questionText": " Too much official formality",
    "answerText": " Red- Tapism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78601,
    "questionText": " That which lasts for a short time",
    "answerText": " Transitory"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78602,
    "questionText": " Constant efforts to achieve something",
    "answerText": " Perseverance"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78603,
    "questionText": " An occasion of great importance",
    "answerText": " Momentous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78604,
    "questionText": " To have a very high opinion of oneself",
    "answerText": " Conceited"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78605,
    "questionText": " One who is given to pleasures of the flesh",
    "answerText": " Epicurean"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78606,
    "questionText": " A person who enjoys food and drink of high quality and knows a lot about it",
    "answerText": " Epicure"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78607,
    "questionText": " The sound of a funeral bell",
    "answerText": " Knell"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78608,
    "questionText": " Belief that war and violence are unjustified",
    "answerText": " Pacifism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78609,
    "questionText": " A group of girls",
    "answerText": " Bevy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78610,
    "questionText": " Military waking signal sounded in the morning",
    "answerText": " Reveille"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78611,
    "questionText": " Or A tune that is played to wake soldiers in the morning",
    "answerText": " Reveille"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78612,
    "questionText": " The highest singing voice in women or boys or A music in highest voice",
    "answerText": " Soprano"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78613,
    "questionText": " A song to put babies to sleep",
    "answerText": " Lullaby"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78614,
    "questionText": " A hymn or song, sacred song sung in praise of God",
    "answerText": " Anthem"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78615,
    "questionText": " A sea abounding in islands Or A group of islands",
    "answerText": " Archipelago"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78616,
    "questionText": " A short walk for pleasure or exercise",
    "answerText": " Stroll"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78617,
    "questionText": " To move along with quick, short twistings",
    "answerText": " Wriggle"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78618,
    "questionText": " One who possesses many talents",
    "answerText": " Versatile"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78619,
    "questionText": " A dramatic performance Or An entertainment in dumb show",
    "answerText": " Masque"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78620,
    "questionText": " One who can use either of his hands with ease",
    "answerText": " Ambidextrous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78621,
    "questionText": " A person who is skilled in horsemanship",
    "answerText": " Equestrian"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78622,
    "questionText": " Extreme of old age when a man behaves like a fool",
    "answerText": " Dotage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78623,
    "questionText": " That can be felt or touched",
    "answerText": " Palpable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78624,
    "questionText": " One who has suddenly gained new wealth, power or prestige",
    "answerText": " Parvenu"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78625,
    "questionText": " A short journey made by a group of persons together",
    "answerText": " Excursion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78626,
    "questionText": " That which makes it difficult to recognize the presence of real nature of somebody or something",
    "answerText": " Camouflage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78627,
    "questionText": " One who thinks that human nature is essentially evil.",
    "answerText": " Cynic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78628,
    "questionText": " A style in which a writer makes a display of his knowledge",
    "answerText": " Pedantic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78629,
    "questionText": " A person pretending to be somebody he is not",
    "answerText": " Impostor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78630,
    "questionText": " One who specialises in the study of birds",
    "answerText": " Ornithologist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78631,
    "questionText": " To mediate between two parties in a dispute.",
    "answerText": " Intercede"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78632,
    "questionText": " Something which is not thorough or profound",
    "answerText": " Superficial"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78633,
    "questionText": " A house for storing grains",
    "answerText": " Granary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78634,
    "questionText": " A light sailing boat built especially for racing",
    "answerText": " Yacht"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78635,
    "questionText": " The original inhabitants of a country",
    "answerText": " Aborigines"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78636,
    "questionText": " A short stay at a place",
    "answerText": " Sojourn"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78637,
    "questionText": " Opposed to great or sudden change",
    "answerText": " Consenrative"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78638,
    "questionText": " Relationship by blood or birth",
    "answerText": " Consanguinity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78639,
    "questionText": " A person living permanently in a certain place",
    "answerText": " Domicile"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78640,
    "questionText": " Anything written in a letter after it is signed",
    "answerText": " Postscript"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78641,
    "questionText": " To cause troops etc to spread out in readiness for battle",
    "answerText": " Deploy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78642,
    "questionText": " A person who is too concerned with small details or rules especially when learning or teaching Or one who makes a vain display of his learning, a conceited fellow",
    "answerText": " Pedant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78643,
    "questionText": " Winding sheet of a corpse",
    "answerText": " Shroud"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78644,
    "questionText": " According to custom",
    "answerText": " Customary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78645,
    "questionText": " Abnormally high blood pressure",
    "answerText": " Hypertension"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78646,
    "questionText": " Art of beautiful handwriting",
    "answerText": " Calligraphy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78647,
    "questionText": " All the customs and beliefs of a society",
    "answerText": " Tradition"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78648,
    "questionText": " Art or craft needing skill with hand",
    "answerText": " Handicraft"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78649,
    "questionText": " Art of growing vegetables, fruit, flowers.",
    "answerText": " Horticulture"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78650,
    "questionText": " Art and science of building construction",
    "answerText": " Architecture"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78651,
    "questionText": " An author's explanatory remarks at the beginning of a book",
    "answerText": " Preface"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78652,
    "questionText": " Bearing young by eggs",
    "answerText": " Oviparous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78653,
    "questionText": " Bearing living young",
    "answerText": " Viviparous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78654,
    "questionText": " Belief not based on reason or knowledge",
    "answerText": " superstition"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78655,
    "questionText": " Belonging to long past",
    "answerText": " Ancient"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78656,
    "questionText": " A board of directors in a company",
    "answerText": " Directorate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78657,
    "questionText": " A body of voters",
    "answerText": " Electorate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78658,
    "questionText": " A brief account of a subject",
    "answerText": " Summary/Compendium"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78659,
    "questionText": " Capable of being wounded",
    "answerText": " Vulnerable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78660,
    "questionText": " Fond of much alcoholic drink",
    "answerText": " Bibulous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78661,
    "questionText": " A person who is foolishly fond of one's wife.",
    "answerText": " Henpecked/Uxorious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78662,
    "questionText": " A person who helps in a wrong deed or crime",
    "answerText": " Accomplice/ Accessary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78663,
    "questionText": " Helpful but not an essential part",
    "answerText": " Accessory"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78664,
    "questionText": " A holy or sacred place",
    "answerText": " Sanctuary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78665,
    "questionText": " Honesty and uprightness of character",
    "answerText": " Integrity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78666,
    "questionText": " That which cannot be altered",
    "answerText": " Unajlterable/ Irrevocable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78667,
    "questionText": " Killing of large numbers of defenceless people",
    "answerText": " Massacre"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78668,
    "questionText": " The murder for political reasons",
    "answerText": " Assassination"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78669,
    "questionText": " The murder of one's sister",
    "answerText": " Sorocide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78670,
    "questionText": " The murder of one's husband",
    "answerText": " Mariticide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78671,
    "questionText": " One who always gets into trouble",
    "answerText": " Scapegrace"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78672,
    "questionText": " One who fluently speaks many languages",
    "answerText": " Polygot"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78673,
    "questionText": " One who goes for a secret official mission",
    "answerText": " Emissary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78674,
    "questionText": " One who habitually talks while sleeping.",
    "answerText": " Somniloquist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78675,
    "questionText": " One who walks while asleep",
    "answerText": " Somnambulist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78676,
    "questionText": " One who is excessively patriotic",
    "answerText": " Chauvinist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78677,
    "questionText": " One who makes a secret plan against somebody",
    "answerText": " Conspirator"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78678,
    "questionText": " One who receives something",
    "answerText": " Recipient"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78679,
    "questionText": " One who regains health and strength after illness",
    "answerText": " Convalescent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78680,
    "questionText": " One who plans to destroy all governments",
    "answerText": " Anarchist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78681,
    "questionText": " One who studies the mind",
    "answerText": " Psychologist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78682,
    "questionText": " One who speaks two languages",
    "answerText": " Bilingual"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78683,
    "questionText": " One who takes an active part in politics",
    "answerText": " Activist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78684,
    "questionText": " One who witnesses secretly to private conversation.",
    "answerText": " Eavesdropper"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78685,
    "questionText": " A permanent military station",
    "answerText": " Cantonment"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78686,
    "questionText": " A person who belongs to a region from earliest time",
    "answerText": " Aboriginal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78687,
    "questionText": " A perfect happiness",
    "answerText": " Ecstasy/Bliss"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78688,
    "questionText": " A person who holds a high office",
    "answerText": " Dignitary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78689,
    "questionText": " A person who is kept as a prisoner",
    "answerText": " Captive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78690,
    "questionText": " A person who takes part in state affairs",
    "answerText": " Statesman"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78691,
    "questionText": " A person who files a suit",
    "answerText": " Plaintiff"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78692,
    "questionText": " A person who uses disruptive forces to bring about political or social change",
    "answerText": " Extremist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78693,
    "questionText": " A policy of extending a country's empire and influence",
    "answerText": " Imperialism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78694,
    "questionText": " Persuade by flattery",
    "answerText": " Cajole"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78695,
    "questionText": " A political system without opposition.",
    "answerText": " Totalitarianism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78696,
    "questionText": " A person who is reserved in speech",
    "answerText": " Reticent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78697,
    "questionText": " Science of poisons",
    "answerText": " Toxicology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78698,
    "questionText": " Science of the fossils",
    "answerText": " Palaentology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78699,
    "questionText": " A temple dedicated to all the gods",
    "answerText": " Pantheon"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78700,
    "questionText": " That which can easily be curved without breaking.",
    "answerText": " Flexible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78701,
    "questionText": " That which eats grass",
    "answerText": " Herbivore /Herbivorous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78702,
    "questionText": " That which has very harmful and dangerous effects.",
    "answerText": " Detrimental"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78703,
    "questionText": " That which is corpse like",
    "answerText": " Cadaverous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78704,
    "questionText": " That which is cat like",
    "answerText": " Feline"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78705,
    "questionText": " That which is cow like",
    "answerText": " Bowine"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78706,
    "questionText": " That which is fish like",
    "answerText": " Piscine"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78707,
    "questionText": " That which is morally dangerous",
    "answerText": " Pestiferous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78708,
    "questionText": " That which is prohibited by law",
    "answerText": " Prohibitory"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78709,
    "questionText": " A whole body of wage earners",
    "answerText": " Proletariat"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78710,
    "questionText": " The word whose meaning is difficult to understand",
    "answerText": " Abstruse"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78711,
    "questionText": " Writing material pen, paper etc",
    "answerText": " Stationery"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78712,
    "questionText": " An outline of a play, opera",
    "answerText": " Scenario"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78713,
    "questionText": " A woman who entertains guests",
    "answerText": " Hostess"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78714,
    "questionText": " A vehicle which is used to carry a sick or wounded person",
    "answerText": " Ambulance"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78715,
    "questionText": " A vehicle which is used to carry a dead body",
    "answerText": " Hearse"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78716,
    "questionText": " A person who is very cruel",
    "answerText": " Fiend"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78717,
    "questionText": " A written statement which gives us information",
    "answerText": " Memorandum"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78718,
    "questionText": " A person who visits other countries for pleasure",
    "answerText": " Tourist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78719,
    "questionText": " A thing which can easily be broken",
    "answerText": " Fragile"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78720,
    "questionText": " Looking upon dark side of things",
    "answerText": " Pessimism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78721,
    "questionText": " A person who looks at the dark side of things",
    "answerText": " Pessimist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78722,
    "questionText": " Looking upon bright side of things",
    "answerText": " Optimism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78723,
    "questionText": " A person who looks at the bright side of things",
    "answerText": " Optimist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78724,
    "questionText": " An idle talk",
    "answerText": " Gossip"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78725,
    "questionText": " That which cannot be understood",
    "answerText": " Incomprehensible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78726,
    "questionText": " A substance which is used to kill an insect",
    "answerText": " Insecticide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78727,
    "questionText": " A substance which is used to kill a germ",
    "answerText": " Germicide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78728,
    "questionText": " A substance which prevents wound from germs",
    "answerText": " Antiseptic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78729,
    "questionText": " A swelling part of a body",
    "answerText": " Int1ammation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78730,
    "questionText": " A person who is a specialist in pregnancy and childbirth",
    "answerText": " Obstetrician"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78731,
    "questionText": " A speech/ statement which is delivered without preparation",
    "answerText": " Extempore"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78732,
    "questionText": " A person who is a specialist in bone disease",
    "answerText": " Orthopaedist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78733,
    "questionText": " A woman who is a specialist in reproductive organs",
    "answerText": " Gyanaecologist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78734,
    "questionText": " A person who is a specialist in heart disease.",
    "answerText": " Cardiologist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78735,
    "questionText": " A person who is a specialist in nervous system",
    "answerText": " Neurologist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78736,
    "questionText": " A person who is a specialist in child disease",
    "answerText": " Pediatrician"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78737,
    "questionText": " A reminder of something",
    "answerText": " Memento"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78738,
    "questionText": " A person who examines teeth",
    "answerText": " Dentist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78739,
    "questionText": " A person who examines eyesight and sells glasses",
    "answerText": " Optician"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78740,
    "questionText": " A group of ship",
    "answerText": " Fleet"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78741,
    "questionText": " A person who eat human flesh",
    "answerText": " Cannibal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78742,
    "questionText": " : Persons living at the same time",
    "answerText": " Contemporary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78743,
    "questionText": " Person having the same opinions",
    "answerText": " Unanimous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78744,
    "questionText": " A plant or an animal which lives on another",
    "answerText": " Parasite"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78745,
    "questionText": " A child whose parents are dead",
    "answerText": " Orphan"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78746,
    "questionText": " A person who is a great lover of his country",
    "answerText": " Patriot"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78747,
    "questionText": " A person who brings in goods from a foreign country",
    "answerText": " Importer"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78748,
    "questionText": " A person who sends goods to another country",
    "answerText": " Exporter"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78749,
    "questionText": " The dead body of a human being",
    "answerText": " Corpse"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78750,
    "questionText": " The dead body of an animal",
    "answerText": " Carcase"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78751,
    "questionText": " A person who writes the life history of another person",
    "answerText": " Biographer"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78752,
    "questionText": " A person who writes his life history",
    "answerText": " Autobiographer"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78753,
    "questionText": " The life history of a person written by himself",
    "answerText": " Autobiography"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78754,
    "questionText": " The life history of a person written by another",
    "answerText": " Biography"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78755,
    "questionText": " A man who remains unmarried",
    "answerText": " Bachelor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78756,
    "questionText": " A woman who remains unmarried",
    "answerText": " Spinster/maid"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78757,
    "questionText": " One who can read and write",
    "answerText": " Literate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78758,
    "questionText": " One who cannot read and write",
    "answerText": " Illiterate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78759,
    "questionText": " One who believes in the existence of God",
    "answerText": " Theist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78760,
    "questionText": " One who does not believe in the existence of God",
    "answerText": " Atheist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78761,
    "questionText": " A person who lives in a foreign country",
    "answerText": " Alien"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78762,
    "questionText": " A person who leaves his own country and goes to settle in another",
    "answerText": " Emigrant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78763,
    "questionText": " A medicine which induces vomiting",
    "answerText": " Emetic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78764,
    "questionText": " That cannot be exhausted",
    "answerText": " Inexhaustible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78765,
    "questionText": " A person who comes to one country from another to settle",
    "answerText": " Immigrant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78766,
    "questionText": " One who commits the first act of attack",
    "answerText": " Aggressor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78767,
    "questionText": " One who is all powerful",
    "answerText": " Omnipotent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78768,
    "questionText": " One who is present everywhere",
    "answerText": " Omnipresent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78769,
    "questionText": " One who knows everything",
    "answerText": " Omniscient"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78770,
    "questionText": " One who believes in fate",
    "answerText": " Fatalist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78771,
    "questionText": " One who loves mankind",
    "answerText": " Philanthropist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78772,
    "questionText": " One who plays, sings, paints pictures etc not for money, but for the love of it",
    "answerText": " Amateur"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78773,
    "questionText": " The letters used in writing a language",
    "answerText": " Alphabet"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78774,
    "questionText": " Yearly return of the date of an event",
    "answerText": " Anniversary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78775,
    "questionText": " A substance like ether, chloroform",
    "answerText": " Anaesthetic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78776,
    "questionText": " A person who is skilled in making analysis",
    "answerText": " Analyst"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78777,
    "questionText": " One who eats too much",
    "answerText": " Glutton"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78778,
    "questionText": " A female of gander",
    "answerText": " Goose"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78779,
    "questionText": " A place of shelter for ships",
    "answerText": " Harbour"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78780,
    "questionText": " An equipment of a horse",
    "answerText": " Harness"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78781,
    "questionText": " A spear on a rope for catching whales and other larger fish",
    "answerText": " Harpoon"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78782,
    "questionText": " An adult male of deer",
    "answerText": " Hart"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78783,
    "questionText": " A plane figure of seven sides",
    "answerText": " Heptagon"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78784,
    "questionText": " A number of animals kept feeding or travelling together",
    "answerText": " Herd"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78785,
    "questionText": " A plane figure with six sides",
    "answerText": " Hexagon"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78786,
    "questionText": " A person who takes part in a hijack",
    "answerText": " Hijacker"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78787,
    "questionText": " A word that is the same in sound as another but different in meaning",
    "answerText": " Homonym"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78788,
    "questionText": " A supreme ruler",
    "answerText": " Monarch"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78789,
    "questionText": " A holiday which is taken by a newly married couple",
    "answerText": " Honeymoon"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78790,
    "questionText": " A diagram of the heavens showing the relative position of planets at the time of a person's death",
    "answerText": " Horoscope"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78791,
    "questionText": " A person who entertains guests",
    "answerText": " Host"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78792,
    "questionText": " A woman who entertains guest",
    "answerText": " Hostess"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78793,
    "questionText": " A dog used for hunting",
    "answerText": " Hound"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78794,
    "questionText": " A person who carries off somebody by force",
    "answerText": " Kidnapper"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78795,
    "questionText": " A place where clothes are washed and pressed",
    "answerText": " Laundry"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78796,
    "questionText": " An army officer who is below a captain in rank.",
    "answerText": " Lieutenant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78797,
    "questionText": " or, A junior officer in the navy",
    "answerText": " Lieutenant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78798,
    "questionText": " Any alcoholic drink",
    "answerText": " Liquor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78799,
    "questionText": " A baggage of a traveller",
    "answerText": " Luggage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78800,
    "questionText": " A young unmarried woman",
    "answerText": " Maiden"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78801,
    "questionText": " A speech which is delivered for the first time",
    "answerText": " Maiden Speech"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78802,
    "questionText": " An animal that feeds its young with milk from the female mammary glands",
    "answerText": " Mammal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78803,
    "questionText": " A book, document, letter etc written by hand or typed",
    "answerText": " Manuscript"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78804,
    "questionText": " A female of donkey /horse",
    "answerText": " Mare"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78805,
    "questionText": " A woman who is in charge of nursing in a hospital",
    "answerText": " Matron"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78806,
    "questionText": " A tiny living organism causing disease",
    "answerText": " Microbe"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78807,
    "questionText": " An optical instrument for magnifying objects",
    "answerText": " Microscope"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78808,
    "questionText": " A place where coins are made",
    "answerText": " Mint"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78809,
    "questionText": " An official record of the proceeding of a meeting.",
    "answerText": " Minutes"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78810,
    "questionText": " An impudent girl",
    "answerText": " Minx"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78811,
    "questionText": " An examiner presiding at some university examinations",
    "answerText": " Moderator"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78812,
    "questionText": " A building in which monks live",
    "answerText": " Monastery"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78813,
    "questionText": " Apupil who looks after the boys in the class in the absence of the teacher",
    "answerText": " Monitor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78814,
    "questionText": " A person who has withdrawn from the world for religious reasons",
    "answerText": " Monk"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78815,
    "questionText": " Two or more than two letters combined in one design",
    "answerText": " Monogram"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78816,
    "questionText": " A drama to be performed by a single man",
    "answerText": " Monologue"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78817,
    "questionText": " A building which is constructed to keep alive one's memory",
    "answerText": " Monument"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78818,
    "questionText": " A hotel for the motorists, in which parking and servicing facilities are available",
    "answerText": " Motel"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78819,
    "questionText": " A building where works of art, scientific specimens and other objects of permanent value are kept and displayed.",
    "answerText": " Museum"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78820,
    "questionText": " Flesh of sheep used as food",
    "answerText": " Mutton"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78821,
    "questionText": " Secretion of a plant which attracts the insects or birds that pollinate flowers",
    "answerText": " Nectar"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78822,
    "questionText": " A room or place set a part for children",
    "answerText": " Nursery"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78823,
    "questionText": " A place where young plants and trees are raised for transplantation elsewhere",
    "answerText": " Nursery"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78824,
    "questionText": " A lovely young girl",
    "answerText": " Nymph"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78825,
    "questionText": " A company of performers playing musical instruments",
    "answerText": " Orchestra"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78826,
    "questionText": " A person who looks after horses at an inn",
    "answerText": " Ostler"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78827,
    "questionText": " A plane figure of the shape of an egg",
    "answerText": " Oval"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78828,
    "questionText": " A person who tells the future and interprets character by reading the lines and configuration on the palm",
    "answerText": " Palmist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78829,
    "questionText": " Remedy for all diseases",
    "answerText": " Panacea"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78830,
    "questionText": " An event which happens once in two years",
    "answerText": " Biennial"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78831,
    "questionText": " An event which happens once in three years",
    "answerText": " Triennial"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78832,
    "questionText": " An event which happens once in four years",
    "answerText": " Quadrennial"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78833,
    "questionText": " An event which happens once in five years",
    "answerText": " Quinquennial"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78834,
    "questionText": " An event which happens once in six years",
    "answerText": " Sexennial"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78835,
    "questionText": " An event which happens once in seven years",
    "answerText": " Septennial"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78836,
    "questionText": " An event which happens once in eight years.",
    "answerText": " Octennial"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78837,
    "questionText": " An event which happens once in ten year",
    "answerText": " Decennial"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78838,
    "questionText": " One who makes a scientific study of language",
    "answerText": " Linguist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78839,
    "questionText": " A person who lives on vegetables",
    "answerText": " Vegetarian"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78840,
    "questionText": " A person who eats vegetables and meat",
    "answerText": " Non- vegetarian"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78841,
    "questionText": " One who believes in oneself",
    "answerText": " Egoist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78842,
    "questionText": " One who wastes money for luxury",
    "answerText": " Extravagant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78843,
    "questionText": " One who abandons his religious faith",
    "answerText": " Apostate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78844,
    "questionText": " A person who has a long experience of any occupation",
    "answerText": " Veteran"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78845,
    "questionText": " An animal which gives milk and suckles its young one",
    "answerText": " Mammal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78846,
    "questionText": " Baggage of a traveller",
    "answerText": " Luggage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78847,
    "questionText": " A place where fishes and water plants are kept",
    "answerText": " Aquarium"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78848,
    "questionText": " A person who plays violin",
    "answerText": " Violinist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78849,
    "questionText": " An area of land planted with grapes",
    "answerText": " Vineyard"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78850,
    "questionText": " A man or woman who has not sexual experience.",
    "answerText": " Virgin"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78851,
    "questionText": " Something that happens without a cause",
    "answerText": " Accident"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78852,
    "questionText": " A person whose profession is to keep accounts",
    "answerText": " Accountant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78853,
    "questionText": " Person with whom one is acquainted",
    "answerText": " Acquaintance"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78854,
    "questionText": " A set of instruments put together for a purpose",
    "answerText": " Apparatus"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78855,
    "questionText": " A legal written statement",
    "answerText": " Affidavit"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78856,
    "questionText": " A ground for the arrival and departure of aeroplanes",
    "answerText": " Aerodrome"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78857,
    "questionText": " One who is engaged in husbandry",
    "answerText": " Agriculturist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78858,
    "questionText": " One who drives an aeroplane",
    "answerText": " Pilot/Aeronaut"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78859,
    "questionText": " The bony framework of the body",
    "answerText": " Skeleton"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78860,
    "questionText": " A book giving information on every department of knowledge in alphabetical order",
    "answerText": " Encyclopedia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78861,
    "questionText": " A building in which dead bodies are burnt.",
    "answerText": " Crematorium"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78862,
    "questionText": " That which can be easily set on fire",
    "answerText": " Inflammable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78863,
    "questionText": " A portable radio set",
    "answerText": " Transistor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78864,
    "questionText": " A change in shape, size, appearance, quality etc",
    "answerText": " Transformation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78865,
    "questionText": " A company of persons such as pilgrims, merchants making a journey together for safety",
    "answerText": " Caravan"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78866,
    "questionText": " Plans and promises which are declared by a candidate before the people in election",
    "answerText": " Manifesto"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78867,
    "questionText": " A disease that is found regularly in a particular place",
    "answerText": " Endemic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78868,
    "questionText": " A disease that causes death",
    "answerText": " Fatal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78869,
    "questionText": " A disease that affects many people at the same place and time",
    "answerText": " Epidemic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78870,
    "questionText": " A disease widely epidemic",
    "answerText": " Pandemic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78871,
    "questionText": " An animal that creeps/ crawls and lays eggs",
    "answerText": " Reptile"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78872,
    "questionText": " Colouring matter of green part of plants",
    "answerText": " Chlorophyll"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78873,
    "questionText": " Hundredth anniversary",
    "answerText": " Centenary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78874,
    "questionText": " A chemical used for surface cleaning",
    "answerText": " Detergent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78875,
    "questionText": " A person who is authorised to execute a legal deed",
    "answerText": " Executor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78876,
    "questionText": " A person who is appointed to carry out the provisions of one's will",
    "answerText": " Executor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78877,
    "questionText": " The act of killing one's brother",
    "answerText": " Patricide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78878,
    "questionText": " That which cannot be read",
    "answerText": " Illegible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78879,
    "questionText": " A definite system of naming especially in classification",
    "answerText": " Nomenclature"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78880,
    "questionText": " An unscrupulous person who puts experience before principle",
    "answerText": " Opportunist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78881,
    "questionText": " State of being of one mind",
    "answerText": " Unanimous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78882,
    "questionText": " A person who broad cast something alive",
    "answerText": " Commentator"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78883,
    "questionText": " A set of terms",
    "answerText": " Ultimatum"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78884,
    "questionText": " That which cannot be burnt",
    "answerText": " Incombustible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78885,
    "questionText": " An instrument which is used to view objects at a distance",
    "answerText": " Telescope"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78886,
    "questionText": " A journey by sea",
    "answerText": " Voyage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78887,
    "questionText": " A list of books and writings of an author",
    "answerText": " Bibliography"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78888,
    "questionText": " A door which opens into rooms by a narrow passage",
    "answerText": " Corridor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78889,
    "questionText": " A lover of good meals",
    "answerText": " Gourmand"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78890,
    "questionText": " A person who breaks into a house to steal",
    "answerText": " Burglar"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78891,
    "questionText": " A person who brings goods illegally",
    "answerText": " Smuggler"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78892,
    "questionText": " A person who purchases goods from a shop",
    "answerText": " Customer"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78893,
    "questionText": " A person who interviews someone",
    "answerText": " Interviewer"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78894,
    "questionText": " A person who always reads books",
    "answerText": " Bookworm"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78895,
    "questionText": " A person who is very careful in the use of money",
    "answerText": " Economical/frugal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78896,
    "questionText": " A person who lives and works for others",
    "answerText": " Altruist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78897,
    "questionText": " A person who travels in space",
    "answerText": " Astronaut"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78898,
    "questionText": " A person who travels to a holy place",
    "answerText": " Pilgrim"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78899,
    "questionText": " A person who walks",
    "answerText": " Pedestrian"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78900,
    "questionText": " From one generation to another",
    "answerText": " Hereditary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78901,
    "questionText": " A period of ten years",
    "answerText": " Decade"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78902,
    "questionText": " A person who is forced to flee to shelter",
    "answerText": " Refugee"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78903,
    "questionText": " A person who is sent to other country to propagate religion",
    "answerText": " Missionary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78904,
    "questionText": " Land that does not grow anything",
    "answerText": " Barren"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78905,
    "questionText": " A person who prepares and sells drugs",
    "answerText": " Druggist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78906,
    "questionText": " A person who runs a beauty parlour",
    "answerText": " Beautician"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78907,
    "questionText": " A person who frightens and wants to achieve his goals",
    "answerText": " Terrorist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78908,
    "questionText": " A person who works against his country",
    "answerText": " Traitor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78909,
    "questionText": " A person who is uncivilized",
    "answerText": " Barbarian"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78910,
    "questionText": " A person who is employed in armed forces",
    "answerText": " Personnel"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78911,
    "questionText": " A place where clothes are kept",
    "answerText": " Wardrobe"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78912,
    "questionText": " A place where dead bodies are buried",
    "answerText": " Cemetery"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78913,
    "questionText": " A building in which people sit to listen to songs, music etc",
    "answerText": " Auditorium"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78914,
    "questionText": " A place in which bees are kept",
    "answerText": " Apiary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78915,
    "questionText": " A place in which birds are kept",
    "answerText": " Aviary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78916,
    "questionText": " A planned activity",
    "answerText": " Campaign"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78917,
    "questionText": " A medical examination of a dead body",
    "answerText": " Postmortem"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78918,
    "questionText": " Amount paid to a man for his labour",
    "answerText": " Remuneration"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78919,
    "questionText": " Soldiers who fight on foot",
    "answerText": " Infantry"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78920,
    "questionText": " Soldiers who fight on horseback",
    "answerText": " Cavalry"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78921,
    "questionText": " Land that grows things in abundance",
    "answerText": " Fertile"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78922,
    "questionText": " That which is no longer in use",
    "answerText": " Obsolete"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78923,
    "questionText": " A person who has a bad reputation",
    "answerText": " Notorious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78924,
    "questionText": " A diplomatic representative in another country",
    "answerText": " Ambassador"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78925,
    "questionText": " A place where arms are kept",
    "answerText": " Armoury"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78926,
    "questionText": " A person who studies stars, planets and other heavenly bodies",
    "answerText": " Astronomer"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78927,
    "questionText": " A group of ants",
    "answerText": " Swarm"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78928,
    "questionText": " A period of 15days",
    "answerText": " Fortnight"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78929,
    "questionText": " A list of books",
    "answerText": " Catalogue"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78930,
    "questionText": " A blind adherent to creed",
    "answerText": " Bigot"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78931,
    "questionText": " An instrument for measuring the pressure of the atmosphere",
    "answerText": " Barometer"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78932,
    "questionText": " The murder of one's wife",
    "answerText": " Uxoricide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78933,
    "questionText": " A large retail store.",
    "answerText": " Emporium"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78934,
    "questionText": " A large destruction by fire.",
    "answerText": " Holocaust"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78935,
    "questionText": " A law making body of a country / state.",
    "answerText": " Legislature"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78936,
    "questionText": " A legal enquiry to find out faults.",
    "answerText": " Inquisition"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78937,
    "questionText": " A list and explanation of difficult words.",
    "answerText": " Glossary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78938,
    "questionText": " A lover of animals.",
    "answerText": " Philozoic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78939,
    "questionText": " A lover of arts.",
    "answerText": " Philotechnic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78940,
    "questionText": " A lover of dogs.",
    "answerText": " Canophilist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78941,
    "questionText": " A lover of God.",
    "answerText": " Philotheist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78942,
    "questionText": " A lover of learning.",
    "answerText": " Philomath"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78943,
    "questionText": " A lover of women.",
    "answerText": " Philogynist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78944,
    "questionText": " A lover of poetry and art.",
    "answerText": " Philomuse"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78945,
    "questionText": " A marriage of God.",
    "answerText": " Theogamy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78946,
    "questionText": " A medicine that induces sleep.",
    "answerText": " Narcotic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78947,
    "questionText": " A name derived from father's name.",
    "answerText": " Patronymic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78948,
    "questionText": " That which is not composed of matter.",
    "answerText": " Incorporeal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78949,
    "questionText": " A notice of the death of a person.",
    "answerText": " Obituary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78950,
    "questionText": " One who cannot die.",
    "answerText": " Immortal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78951,
    "questionText": " An admirer of art.",
    "answerText": " Dilettante"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78952,
    "questionText": " A man having the qualities of women.",
    "answerText": " Effeminate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78953,
    "questionText": " That which cannot be moved.",
    "answerText": " Immobile"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78954,
    "questionText": " The study of insects.",
    "answerText": " Entomology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78955,
    "questionText": " Science of human beauty.",
    "answerText": " Kalology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78956,
    "questionText": " Science of fixing dates.",
    "answerText": " Chronology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78957,
    "questionText": " Science of crimes and criminals.",
    "answerText": " Criminology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78958,
    "questionText": " Study of coins.",
    "answerText": " Numismatics"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78959,
    "questionText": " Science of climate.",
    "answerText": " Climatology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78960,
    "questionText": " Science of blood.",
    "answerText": " Haematology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78961,
    "questionText": " Science of birds.",
    "answerText": " Ornithology"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78962,
    "questionText": " Rise or fall in the level of the sea.",
    "answerText": " Tide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78963,
    "questionText": " Right or advantage available to a person.",
    "answerText": " Privilege"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78964,
    "questionText": " Reward for a work or service.",
    "answerText": " Remuneration"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78965,
    "questionText": " Return to one's own country.",
    "answerText": " Repatriate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78966,
    "questionText": " Return the same sort of ill treatment.",
    "answerText": " Retaliate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78967,
    "questionText": " Reduction in a tax or debt.",
    "answerText": " Rebate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78968,
    "questionText": " Religious discourse.",
    "answerText": " Sermon"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78969,
    "questionText": " Reserved in speech.",
    "answerText": " Reticent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78970,
    "questionText": " Responsible according to law.",
    "answerText": " Liable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78971,
    "questionText": " Restore to former position.",
    "answerText": " Rehabilitate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78972,
    "questionText": " Public merry making and feasting.",
    "answerText": " Carnival"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78973,
    "questionText": " Public activity which take place in"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78974,
    "questionText": " Colourful and expensive way.",
    "answerText": " Extravaganza"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78975,
    "questionText": " Place of good climate for invalids.",
    "answerText": " Asylum"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78976,
    "questionText": " Property left to someone by a will.",
    "answerText": " Legacy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78977,
    "questionText": " Habit of independent thought.",
    "answerText": " Individualism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78978,
    "questionText": " Prevention of loss, waste, damage.",
    "answerText": " Conservation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78979,
    "questionText": " Prevent from being carried out.",
    "answerText": " Circumvent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78980,
    "questionText": " Pretence of having a virtuous character.",
    "answerText": " Hypocrisy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78981,
    "questionText": " Present form or before birth.",
    "answerText": " Congenital"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78982,
    "questionText": " Marriage of God.",
    "answerText": " Theogamy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78983,
    "questionText": " Lover of dogs.",
    "answerText": " Canophilist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78984,
    "questionText": " Loss of memory.",
    "answerText": " Amnesia"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78985,
    "questionText": " A group of talkative girls / women.",
    "answerText": " Gaggle"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78986,
    "questionText": " Guided by one's sense of duty.",
    "answerText": " Conscientious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78987,
    "questionText": " Gust of wind.",
    "answerText": " Draught"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78988,
    "questionText": " Government by divine laws.",
    "answerText": " Theocracy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78989,
    "questionText": " Government by a king / queen.",
    "answerText": " Monarchy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78990,
    "questionText": " Government by a few people.",
    "answerText": " Oligarchy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78991,
    "questionText": " Governing body of a university.",
    "answerText": " Senate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78992,
    "questionText": " Hater of books.",
    "answerText": " Misobiblic"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78993,
    "questionText": " Hater of learning.",
    "answerText": " Misologist"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78994,
    "questionText": " A garland of flowers.",
    "answerText": " Wreath"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78995,
    "questionText": " Give tit for tat.",
    "answerText": " Retaliate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78996,
    "questionText": " Departure of many people.",
    "answerText": " Exodus"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78997,
    "questionText": " Gift of money to a retiring people.",
    "answerText": " Gratuity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78998,
    "questionText": " Give the right to vote.",
    "answerText": " Enfranchise"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 78999,
    "questionText": " Greedy for money.",
    "answerText": " Repacious"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 79000,
    "questionText": " General instructions.",
    "answerText": " Directive"
  }
]